Guide to the Treasurer, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Benefactors, 1700-1963; Series IV
  - Estates Completed
    - Marsh Estate: executor's correspondence, 1899-1926, undated (Box 406, Folder 656-660)
    - Marsh Estate: executor's letterbook, 1899-1900 (Box 406, Folder 661)
    - Marsh Estate: papers concerning the auction of furniture, art, and plants, 1900 (Box 407, Folder 662)
    - Marsh Estate: legal papers concerning the estate of George Peabody, 1926, undated (Box 407, Folder 663)
    - Marsh Estate: land records, 1876-1888 (Box 407, Folder 664)
    - Marsh Estate: bankbook, checkbook, and journal of the executors, 1899-1923 (Box 407, Folder 665)
    - Marsh Estate: bills and receipts, 1899-1917 (Box 407, Folder 666-670)
    - Marsh Estate: clippings and printed matter, 1898, 1899 (Box 407, Folder 671)
    - Marshall, James, 1896, 1900 (Box 408, Folder 672)
    - Martin, Eleanor T., 1947 (Box 408, Folder 673)
    - Martin, Laura P., 1958 (Box 408, Folder 674)
    - Mason, George Grant, 1954 (Box 408, Folder 675)
    - Mather, Alice K., 1951 (Box 408, Folder 676)
    - Mathewson, Allen, 1950 (Box 408, Folder 677)
    - Matthews, Annabel McE., 1955 (Box 408, Folder 678)
    - Matthiesson, F. O., 1949 (Box 408, Folder 679)
    - Maxwell, Robert, 1920, 1940-1942 (Box 408, Folder 680)
    - Maxwell, William, 1939, 1941-1942 (Box 408, Folder 681)
    - May, Calvin S., 1918-1919 (Box 408, Folder 682)
    - Mead, Frederick, 1918-1961 (Box 408, Folder 683-685)
    - Mead, Solomon, 1898, 1902 (Box 408, Folder 686)
    - Meara, Frank S., 1925, 1927, 1930, 1934 (Box 408, Folder 687)
    - Meeker, Lucy J., 1955 (Box 408, Folder 688)
    - Menge, George A., 1937 (Box 408, Folder 689)
    - Mercer, Alexander G., 1870, 1884 (Box 408, Folder 690)
    - Mercer, Alexander G., 1911-1939 (Box 409, Folder 691-696)
    - Mercer, Alexander G., 1940-1954 (Box 410, Folder 697-700)
    - Merriam, Ellen R., 1936-1939 (Box 410, Folder 701)
    - Merrifield, Mark E., 1941-1942 (Box 410, Folder 702)
    - Merrow, Joseph M., 1946 (Box 410, Folder 703)
    - Messinger, Charles Raymond, 1941 (Box 410, Folder 704)
    - Meyer, Alfred C., undated (Box 410, Folder 705)
    - Meyer, Walter E., 1957 (Box 410, Folder 706)
    - Middleton, Carrie A., 1934, 1938-1939 (Box 410, Folder 707)
    - Milbank, Dunlevy, 1959-1960 (Box 410, Folder 708)
    - Miller, Alanson D., 1930 (Box 410, Folder 709)
    - Miller, Charles S., 1928, 1932 (Box 410, Folder 710)
    - Miller, Otto, 1921, 1933 (Box 410, Folder 711)
    - Milliken, Seth Minot, 1955, 1957 (Box 410, Folder 712)
    - Minor, Elisha, 1837, 1846 (Box 410, Folder 713)
    - Mitchell, Ruth, 1955 (Box 410, Folder 714)
    - Monroe, Virginia Marquand, 1919, 1928 (Box 410, Folder 715)
    - Moore, Ada Small, 1955 (Box 410, Folder 716)
    - Moore, Douglas S., 1917 (Box 410, Folder 717)
    - Moore, Franklin A., 1939, 1941, 1951 (Box 410, Folder 718)
    - Moorehead, Kate Upshur, 1926 (Box 410, Folder 719)
    - Moran, James T., 1936 (Box 410, Folder 720)
    - Morden, William J., 1957 (Box 410, Folder 721)
    - Morgan, Edwin D., 1882, 1893, 1920 (Box 410, Folder 722)
    - Morgan, H. T., Circa 1883 (Box 410, Folder 723)
    - Morgan, John Hill, 1945, 1947 (Box 411, Folder 724)
    - Morgan, Leila A., 1956 (Box 411, Folder 725)
    - Morris, Edward B., 1926, 1930, 1944 (Box 411, Folder 726)
    - Morris, Edward P., 1939 (Box 411, Folder 727)
    - Moseley, Edward Strong, 1901 (Box 411, Folder 728)
    - Mumford, Anna S., 1854, 1857-1858 (Box 411, Folder 729)
    - Munson, Israel, 1844 (Box 411, Folder 730)
    - Murphy, Esther G., 1945 (Box 411, Folder 731)
    - Murphy, Henry C., 1946 (Box 411, Folder 732)
    - Murphy, Katherine Speed, 1945 (Box 411, Folder 733)
    - Murray, William D., 1940 (Box 411, Folder 734)
    - Musgrave, Wayne M., 1936, 1941 (Box 411, Folder 735)
    - Myers, George Hewitt, 1930 (Box 411, Folder 736)
    - Nairn, John J., 1947 (Box 411, Folder 737)
    - Needelman, William R., 1945 (Box 411, Folder 738)
    - Newell, Edward T., 1936, 1941 (Box 411, Folder 739)
    - Newton, Burkett D., 1941, 1945 (Box 411, Folder 740)
    - Newton, Josephine Stiles, 1946-1949 (Box 411, Folder 741)
    - Nicholas, Robert Hastings, 1955-1956 (Box 411, Folder 742)
    - Nichols, Effingham H., 1912 (Box 411, Folder 743)
    - Nichols, George E., 1936 (Box 411, Folder 744)
    - Niemeyer, John H., 1931, 1935-1942 (Box 411, Folder 745)
    - Nisbet, Jane A., 1914, 1926-1927 (Box 411, Folder 746)
    - Nolen, Alfred E., 1922 (Box 411, Folder 747)
    - Nutt, Henry C., 1942, 1946, 1959 (Box 411, Folder 748)
    - Ochs, Adolph S., 1935 (Box 411, Folder 749)
    - Odom, William M., 1942-1943 (Box 411, Folder 750)
    - Osborn, Frederick W., 1919, 1921 (Box 411, Folder 751)
    - Osborn, Miriam A., 1889, 1896-1897 (Box 411, Folder 752)
    - Osborne, Oliver T., 1939, 1940 (Box 411, Folder 753)
    - Otis, Asa, 1878 (Box 411, Folder 754)
    - Otis, Joseph, 1854, 1856 (Box 411, Folder 755)
    - Overlander, J. Elliot, 1946-1951 (Box 411, Folder 756)
    - Packard, Lewis R., Circa 1889 (Box 411, Folder 757)
    - Page, Charles, 1911 (Box 411, Folder 758)
    - Parish, Roswell, 1954 (Box 411, Folder 759)
    - Parker, Charles F., 1950 (Box 411, Folder 760)
    - Parker, Eliza T., 1898, 1912 (Box 411, Folder 761)
    - Parker, Frank J., 1912 (Box 411, Folder 762)
    - Parker, Frederick S., 1916 (Box 411, Folder 763)
    - Parker, Joseph, 1910 (Box 411, Folder 764)
    - Parker, William N., 1928 (Box 411, Folder 765)
    - Parkin, Alice Temple, 1956 (Box 411, Folder 766)
    - Parks, William H., 1897 (Box 411, Folder 767)
    - Parsons, John C., undated (Box 411, Folder 768)
    - Patterson, Frank M., 1939 (Box 411, Folder 769)
    - Pavey, Jeanne R., 1948-1949, 1957 (Box 411, Folder 770)
    - Payne, Oliver H., 1917 (Box 411, Folder 771)
    - Pease, Jane: will and property records, 1845, 1848-1849 (Box 412, Folder 772)
    - Pease, Jane: correspondence concerning the estate, receipts, and records, 1851-1870 (Box 412, Folder 773-774)
    - Pease, Jane: executor's record book, Circa 1851-1854 (Box 412, Folder 775)
    - Peck, Eliza N. (Box 412, Folder 776)
    - Peck, Tracy, 1921 (Box 412, Folder 777)
    - Peet, Edward Wright, 1946 (Box 412, Folder 778)
    - Peirce, Luther H., 1915 (Box 412, Folder 779)
    - Pennell, Arthur J., 1954 (Box 412, Folder 780)
    - Pennington, William, 1911-1913 (Box 412, Folder 781)
    - Perkins, A. E., [1834?] (Box 412, Folder 782)
    - Perkins, Henry A., 1954 (Box 412, Folder 783)
    - Perkins, Samuel C., 1904 (Box 412, Folder 784)
    - Perkins, Simon, 1846 (Box 412, Folder 785)
    - Perrin, Susan Lester, 1932, 1938 (Box 412, Folder 786)
    - Peters, William A., Jr., 1947 (Box 412, Folder 787)
    - Phelps; William Walter, 1885 (Box 412, Folder 788)
    - Phillips, Andrew Wheeler, 1915-1941 (Box 412, Folder 789-790)
    - Phillips, John H., 1900 (Box 412, Folder 791)
    - Pickersgill, Lily V., 1947-1948 (Box 412, Folder 792)
    - Pidgeon, Edward R., 1932-1939 (Box 412, Folder 793)
    - Pierce, Frank W., 1896-1897 (Box 412, Folder 794)
    - Pierpont, James, 1937, 1939 (Box 412, Folder 795)
    - Pillsbury, Albert E., 1931 (Box 412, Folder 796)
    - Pine, Charles H., 1913, 1915-1927 (Box 412, Folder 797)
    - Pitkin, Walter S., 1903-1904 (Box 412, Folder 798)
    - Porter, Dwight, 1940 (Box 412, Folder 799)
    - Porter, George F., 1927 (Box 412, Folder 800)
    - Porter, Martha Day, 1919, 1922 (Box 412, Folder 801)
    - Pratt, Herbert L., 1945 (Box 413, Folder 802)
    - Preston, Walter Grey, 1951-1953 (Box 413, Folder 803)
    - Prudden, T. Mitchell, 1924 (Box 413, Folder 804)
    - Purselle, Edwin, 1946 (Box 413, Folder 805)
    - Putnam, Henry W., 1936-1944 (Box 413, Folder 806-808)
    - Quintal, Edward J., 1951 (Box 413, Folder 809)
    - Randall, Sands F., 1911 (Box 413, Folder 810)
    - Rankin, Hugh, 1939 (Box 413, Folder 811)
    - Raymond, Freeborn F., 1910 (Box 413, Folder 812)
    - Reckford, John King, 1941-1943 (Box 413, Folder 813)
    - Reed, Edward M., 1892-1927 (Box 414, Folder 814)
    - Reichert, Catharine M., 1937 (Box 414, Folder 815)
    - Reynolds, Ambrose, 1825 (Box 414, Folder 816)
    - Reynolds, Horatio M., 1928-1944 (Box 414, Folder 817)
    - Reynolds, James Bronson, 1922-1924 (Box 414, Folder 818)
    - Reynolds, Maude T., 1931, 1941 (Box 414, Folder 819)
    - Reynolds, William George, 1916, 1922, 1943-1945 (Box 414, Folder 820)
    - Rhoda, George Irving, 1957 (Box 414, Folder 821)
    - Richardson, Anna M., 1932-1933 (Box 414, Folder 822)
    - Richardson, Samuel M., 1929-1932 (Box 414, Folder 823)
    - Rigby, James A. & Henry B.
      See: Box 414A folder 823A
    - Riggs, T. Lawrason, 1938, 1943 (Box 414, Folder 824)
    - Righter, William S., 1930-1931, 1939 (Box 414, Folder 825)
    - Ripley, Alfred L., 1941, 1944 (Box 414, Folder 826)
    - Risteen, Ella W., 1943 (Box 414, Folder 827)
    - Robbins, Howard Chandler, 1952 (Box 414, Folder 828)
    - Robbins, Sarah Stuart, 1908 (Box 414, Folder 829)
    - Robinson, Marinda C., 1925, 1928, 1941, 1947 (Box 414, Folder 830)
    - Rogers, Cornelia H. B., 1910 (Box 414, Folder 831)
    - Rogers, Henry Treat, 1921-1923 (Box 414, Folder 832)
    - Rogers, Samuel T., 1912-1913 (Box 414, Folder 833)
    - Rogers, William A., 1944 (Box 414, Folder 834)
    - Roosa, Dewitt, 1923-1924 (Box 414, Folder 835)
    - Rosenblatt, Albert, 1944 (Box 414, Folder 836)
    - Rosenzweig, Grant I., 1947 (Box 414, Folder 837)
    - Ross, William B., 1897, 1904-1908, 1934 (Box 414, Folder 838)
    - Rowland, Grace Talbot, 1918 (Box 414, Folder 839)
    - Runnals, John Felch Bertram, 1943 (Box 414, Folder 840)
    - Ryerson, Edward L., 1928 (Box 414, Folder 841)
    - Ryerson, Mary Mitchell (Mrs. Edward L.), 1939 (Box 414, Folder 842)
    - Sage, Margaret Olivia, 1911, 1917-1928, 1938 (Box 414, Folder 843-844)
    - Rigby, James A. & Henry B.: Trusts (1 of 2), 1933-1951 (Box 414A, Folder 823A)
    - Rigby, James A. & Henry B.: Trusts (2 of 2), 1933-1951 (Box 414A, Folder 823B)
    - Rigby, Henry B.: Last will & testament, 1940 (Box 414A, Folder 823C)
    - Rigby, Henry B.: Estate, 1943-1966 (Box 414A, Folder 823)
    - Rigby, James A. & Henry B.: Trusts (1 of 2), 1948-1958 (Box 414A, Folder 823E)
    - Rigby, James A. & Henry B.: Trusts (2 of 2), 1948-1958 (Box 414A, Folder 823)
    - Rigby, James A. & Henry B.: Trusts, 1957 (Box 414A, Folder 823G)
    - Salisbury, Edward E., 1901-1920 (Box 415, Folder 845-846)
      See also: box 304, folders 1884-1885
    - Salisbury, Evelyn MacCurdy (Mrs. Edward E.), 1918 (Box 415, Folder 847)
    - Saltus, Rollin Sanford, 1954 (Box 415, Folder 848)
    - Sanders, Henry M., 1921 (Box 415, Folder 849)
    - Sargeant, William P., 1936-1937 (Box 415, Folder 850)
    - Sartorius, Irving A., 1957 (Box 415, Folder 851)
    - Schaefer, Karl A., 1957 (Box 415, Folder 852)
    - Schley, Reeve, III, 1957, 1960 (Box 415, Folder 853)
    - Schram, Herman, 1958 (Box 415, Folder 854)
    - Schramm, Arnold O., 1922 (Box 415, Folder 855)
    - Schuchert, Charles, 1942-1943 (Box 415, Folder 856)
    - Schwab, John C., 1912 (Box 415, Folder 857)
    - Scott, Henry W., 1870, 1872 (Box 415, Folder 858)
    - Scudder, Doremus, 1940 (Box 415, Folder 859)
    - Sedgwick, William T., 1921 (Box 415, Folder 860)
    - Seeley, James R., 1941, 1944 (Box 415, Folder 861)
    - Seesel, Albert, 1909 (Box 415, Folder 862)
    - Selden, Abby S. L., 1929-1930 (Box 415, Folder 863)
    - Sewall, Richard B., 1916, 1918-1919, 1939 (Box 415, Folder 864)
    - Seymour, George, Dudley, 1945 (Box 415, Folder 865)
    - Shaw, Charles H., 1916, 1945-1950 (Box 415, Folder 866)
    - Sheffield, Amelia Daggett (Mrs. George St. John), 1934, 1937 (Box 415, Folder 867)
    - Sheffield, George St. John, 1925, 1937 (Box 415, Folder 868)
    - Sheridan, James, 1960-1962 (Box 415, Folder 869)
    - Sherman, Elizabeth, 1845, 1848-1849 (Box 415, Folder 870)
    - Sherman, Gordon E., 1931 (Box 415, Folder 871)
    - Shockley, Lazelle S., 1940 (Box 415, Folder 872)
    - Shoemaker, Levi, 1909-1928 (Box 416, Folder 873-874)
    - Shortridge, Laura Virginia Watson, 1943, 1946 (Box 416, Folder 875)
    - Sidenberg, William R., 1960, 1961 (Box 416, Folder 876)
    - Sill, Elizabeth, 1915-1916 (Box 416, Folder 877)
      See also: box 321, folders 2058-2062
    - Silliman, Augustus Ely, Circa 1884-1905 (Box 416, Folder 878)
    - Silliman, Benjamin D., 1900-1923 (Box 416, Folder 879)
    - Slade, Francis Louis, 1944 (Box 416, Folder 880)
    - Slade, George T., 1936, 1941-1944 (Box 416, Folder 881)
    - Slade, William Strong, 1927 (Box 416, Folder 882)
    - Sloan, Thomas C., 1886, 1891, 1896-1897 (Box 416, Folder 883)
    - Sloane, William, 1922 (Box 416, Folder 884)
    - Small, Emma M., 1948, 1951 (Box 416, Folder 885)
    - Smith, Bessie Helmer, 1950, 1953 (Box 416, Folder 886)
    - Smith, Charles Henry, 1933-1934 (Box 416, Folder 887)
    - Smith, Charles Robinson, 1929-1930 (Box 416, Folder 888)
    - Smith, David P., 1874 (Box 416, Folder 889)
    - Smith, Douglas T., 1952 (Box 416, Folder 890)
    - Smith, Edwin W., 1937, 1939 (Box 416, Folder 891)
    - Smith, Herbert Knox, 1932 (Box 416, Folder 892)
    - Smith, Loyal L., 1907 (Box 416, Folder 893)
    - Smith, Lucy F., 1946, 1947, 1950 (Box 416, Folder 894)
    - Smith, Marcius C., 1941 (Box 416, Folder 895)
    - Smith, Mary B., 1911, 1922, 1925 (Box 417, Folder 896)
    - Smith, William Barnard, 1950 (Box 417, Folder 897)
    - Snow, Mrs. Alpheus Henry, 1928 (Box 417, Folder 898)
    - Snow, Emily V., 1929 (Box 417, Folder 899)
    - Southworth, Edward Wells, 1902-1909 (Box 417, Folder 900)
    - Spencer, Margaret C., 1948, 1950 (Box 417, Folder 901)
    - Sperry, Watson R., 1927 (Box 417, Folder 902)
    - Sprague, Albert Arnold & Nancy A., 1913, 1915-1916, 1922-1923 (Box 417, Folder 903)
    - Stanley, Katherine A., 1927, 1928 (Box 417, Folder 904)
    - Starkweather, William J., 1952-1954 (Box 417, Folder 905)
    - Stedman, Arthur, 1908 (Box 417, Folder 906)
    - Stedman, Edmund Clarence, 1908 (Box 417, Folder 907)
    - Sterling, Edward, 1909-1910 (Box 417, Folder 908)
    - Sterling, John W., 1915 (Box 417, Folder 909)
    - Stevenson, Grace W., 1926, 1933, 1944 (Box 417, Folder 910)
    - Stevenson, Holland N., 1955, 1959 (Box 417, Folder 911)
    - Stewart, Herbert, 1899 (Box 417, Folder 912)
    - Stille, Charles J., 1899, 1907-1931 (Box 417, Folder 913)
      See also: box 264, folder 1547
    - Stimson, Lewis A., 1914, 1917 (Box 417, Folder 914)
    - Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1958 (Box 417, Folder 915)
    - Strathcona, Lord Donald Alexander, 1914 (Box 417, Folder 916)
    - Street, Augustus Russell, 1863-1866, 1909 (Box 417, Folder 917)
    - Street, Augustus Russell: letterbook with a few loose items, Circa 1831-1857 (Box 417, Folder 918)
    - Street, Augustus Russell: daybooks, 1852-1866 (Box 418, Folder 919-920)
    - Street, Augustus Russell: ledger, Circa 1852-1866 (Box 418, Folder 921)
    - Street, Augustus Russell: Correspondence and bills of S. W. Allis, Lessee of Street's New Haven hotel, Circa 1829-1830, 1844-1852, 1854-1869 (Box 418, Folder 922-925)
    - Street, Augustus Russell: Gardel correspondence and bills with S. W. Allis, Circa 1848-1851, 1868 (Box 418, Folder 926)
    - Street, Caroline M., 1877, 1908, 1912 (Box 419, Folder 927)
    - Strong, Henry H., 1923-1924, 1928-1930 (Box 419, Folder 928)
    - Styles, Flora N., 1917 (Box 419, Folder 929)
    - Sweet, Stanley Adams, 1948 (Box 419, Folder 930)
    - Taft, Henry W., 1943, 1945 (Box 419, Folder 931)
    - Taft, William Howard, 1930 (Box 419, Folder 932)
    - Taintnor, Charles N., 1920 (Box 419, Folder 933)
    - Talcott, Elizabeth G., 1817 (Box 419, Folder 934)
    - Tarbell, Frank Bigelow, 1919-1922 (Box 419, Folder 935)
    - Tarbell, John H., 1926, 1929-1931 (Box 419, Folder 936)
    - Tenney, Daniel G., 1951 (Box 419, Folder 937)
    - Tew, Willis, 1928-1930 (Box 419, Folder 938)
    - Thacher, Thomas, 1919 (Box 419, Folder 939)
    - Thacher, Thomas D., 1948, 1950 (Box 419, Folder 940)
    - Thayer, Charles Snow, 1944 (Box 419, Folder 941)
    - Thayer, George B., 1928-1941 (Box 419, Folder 942)
    - Thomas, Helen, 1946, 1951-1954 (Box 419, Folder 943)
    - Thompson, Miles G., 1942, 1944 (Box 419, Folder 944)
    - Thomson, Asahel, 1866 (Box 419, Folder 945)
    - Thorne, William V. S., 1916 (Box 419, Folder 946)
    - Thornton, James C., 1929, 1940, 1952 (Box 419, Folder 947)
    - Thornton, Lilian K., 1957 (Box 419, Folder 948)
    - Tilson, John Q., 1956-1957 (Box 419, Folder 949)
    - Tompkins, Ray & Sarah Wey, 1918, 1926, 1930-1931 (Box 419, Folder 950)
    - Torrey, Charles C., 1953 (Box 419, Folder 951)
    - Toumey, James W., 1933 (Box 419, Folder 952)
    - Town, Ithiel, [1944] (Box 419, Folder 953)
    - Townsend, Emily Allison, 1927-1928 (Box 419, Folder 954)
    - Townsend, Jane A., 1908, 1910 (Box 419, Folder 955)
    - Treat, Wyllys Baird, 1947 (Box 419, Folder 956)
    - Troescher, Robert, 1925, 1930 (Box 419, Folder 957)
      See also: box 322, folder 2063
    - Trowbridge, Francis B., 1943-1944 (Box 419, Folder 958)
    - Trowbridge, Henry, 1883 (Box 419, Folder 959)
    - Turrell, Edgar A., 1930, 1935 (Box 419, Folder 960)
    - Tuttle, Charles Alling, 1923, 1927-1935 (Box 419, Folder 961)
    - Tuttle, Edwin E., 1939 (Box 419, Folder 962)
    - Tuttle, Fannie Farwell, 1953 (Box 419, Folder 963)
    - Tuttle, Frank D., 1926 (Box 420, Folder 964)
    - Twiss, Julius, 1920 (Box 420, Folder 965)
    - Ullman, Isaac M., 1930-1935 (Box 420, Folder 966)
    - Vanderbilt, Cornelius, 1935, 1940, 1942-1943 (Box 420, Folder 967)
    - Vanderbilt, Frederick, 1939-1944 (Box 420, Folder 968-969)
    - Vanderpoel, Lila Burr Chapman, 1948, 1950-1957 (Box 420, Folder 970)
    - Van Name, Theodora, 1955 (Box 420, Folder 971)
    - Van Nostrand, Sarah, 1897, 1900 (Box 420, Folder 972)
    - Van Riper, Walker, 1960 (Box 420, Folder 973)
    - Van Wagenen, Margaret H., 1944, 1946 (Box 420, Folder 974)
    - Vedder, Harold L., 1943, 1950 (Box 420, Folder 975)
    - Veech, Louise, 1948 (Box 420, Folder 976)
    - Viets, Levi C., 1904-1907, 1921-1953, 1965-1966 (Box 420, Folder 977)
      See also: box 261, folders 1519-1520
    - Vincent, George E., 1941 (Box 420, Folder 978)
    - Wade, John A., 1932-1934 (Box 420, Folder 979)
    - Wadhams, Fred Uri, 1958 (Box 420, Folder 980)
    - Walden, Howard T., 1948 (Box 420, Folder 981)
    - Walden, Katherine K., 1911, 1914, 1916-1917 (Box 420, Folder 982)
    - Wallace, Cornelius Royal, 1945 (Box 420, Folder 983)
    - Ward, Frederick A., 1902 (Box 420, Folder 984)
    - Ward, G. Gilbert, 1953 (Box 420, Folder 985)
    - Ward, Jessie L., 1928-1933 (Box 420, Folder 986)
    - Wardwell, Allen, 1951 (Box 420, Folder 987)
    - Warren, Albert, 1939 (Box 420, Folder 988)
    - Washburn, Caroline, 1892 (Box 420, Folder 989)
    - Weatherby, Una L. F., 1956 (Box 420, Folder 990)
    - Webb, Vanderbilt, 1956-1957 (Box 420, Folder 991)
    - Weeks, Louise M., 1933, 1937 (Box 420, Folder 992)
    - Weeter, John Lloyd, 1931 (Box 420, Folder 993)
    - Welles, John S., 1903 (Box 420, Folder 994)
    - Wellman, Guy, 1938, 1941 (Box 420, Folder 995)
    - Wells, Bradford, 1941 (Box 421, Folder 996)
    - Wells, Gabriel, 1943 (Box 421, Folder 997)
    - Wendell, B. Rush, 1933, 1937-1940 (Box 421, Folder 998)
    - Wetmore, Helen H., 1923-1925 (Box 421, Folder 999)
    - Whalen, Louise B. H., 1958 (Box 421, Folder 1000)
    - Whedon, Susan H., 1942, 1946 (Box 421, Folder 1001)
    - Wheeler, Albert Sproull, 1903-1904 (Box 421, Folder 1002)
      See also: box 324, folder 2088
    - Wheeler, Henry Lord, 1915 (Box 421, Folder 1003)
    - White, Andrew D., 1918 (Box 421, Folder 1004)
    - White, Annie L., 1929, 1931 (Box 421, Folder 1005)
    - White, Harriet H., 1897 (Box 421, Folder 1006)
    - White, Henry C. & Lucy S., 1905, 1914, 1922-1927 (Box 421, Folder 1007)
    - Whitehead, Conkey P., 1941 (Box 421, Folder 1008)
    - Whiting, Arthur B., 1936 (Box 421, Folder 1009)
    - Whitney, Eli, 1825, 1829 (Box 421, Folder 1010)
    - Whitney, Payne, 1927-1932 (Box 421, Folder 1011-1012)
    - Whitney, Wheelock, 1957 (Box 421, Folder 1013)
    - Whittemore, Edward L., 1929-1930 (Box 421, Folder 1014)
    - Whittlesey, George Patten, 1922, 1930-1931 (Box 421, Folder 1015)
    - Wickham, Elizabeth M., 1901 (Box 421, Folder 1016)
    - Williams, Adele H., 1920, 1931 (Box 421, Folder 1017)
    - Williams, Earl T., 1918 (Box 421, Folder 1018)
    - Williams, S. Wells, 1884 (Box 421, Folder 1019)
    - Williams, Thomas S., 1862 (Box 421, Folder 1020)
    - Williams, Wayland Wells, 1945 (Box 421, Folder 1021)
    - Williams, Williams, 1947-1948 (Box 421, Folder 1022)
    - Wilson, Edward A., 1929 (Box 421, Folder 1023)
    - Wilson, Mary Jewett, 1941-1945 (Box 422, Folder 1024)
    - Wiman, Dwight Deere, 1951 (Box 422, Folder 1025)
    - Wing, Frank E., 1923 (Box 422, Folder 1026)
    - Wisser, Nellie R., undated (Box 422, Folder 1027)
    - Wolcott, Henry Roger, 1915, 1921 (Box 422, Folder 1028)
    - Wood, Antoinette E., 1930 (Box 422, Folder 1029)
    - Woodman, Francis J., 1916-1917 (Box 422, Folder 1030)
    - Woodruff, Francis Eben, 1913 (Box 422, Folder 1031)
    - Woodruff, Rollin S., 1937 (Box 422, Folder 1032)
    - Woodward, Frank L.: concerning Mary Farnam Woodward trust, 1922-1945 (Box 422, Folder 1033)
    - Woodward, Sarah C., 1939 (Box 422, Folder 1034)
    - Woolley, Clarence M., 1956 (Box 422, Folder 1035)
    - Woolsey, Theodore S., 1919, 1924, 1929 (Box 422, Folder 1036)
    - Woolsey, Theodore Salisbury, Jr., 1932, 1936 (Box 422, Folder 1037)
    - Wordin, Eliza Barnes, 1924 (Box 422, Folder 1038)
    - Wordin, Fannie L., 1930 (Box 422, Folder 1039)
    - Wright, Glen, 1936, 1941-1942 (Box 422, Folder 1040)
    - Wright, Henry P., 1914, 1918, 1927-1944 (Box 422, Folder 1041)
    - Wright, Howell, 1937 (Box 422, Folder 1042)
    - Wright, Josephine L. H., 1942, 1950 (Box 422, Folder 1043)
    - Yeisley, Katharine Bushnell Gaul, 1924 (Box 422, Folder 1044)
    - York, Samuel A., 1933 (Box 422, Folder 1045)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 422, Folder 1046)
- Investments, circa 1722-1926; Series V
  INVESTMENTS embraces lists and muniments of Yale's income producing properties (real estate, stocks, bonds, and other securities) and the records of income produced from them (rent, dividends, and interest). The series is divided into three sub-series:
  Accounting: Investing Funds
  Real Estate
  Loans and Securities
  Accounting: Investing Funds includes records from the nineteenth century when several special funds were established as general or specific endowments. The income produced from investments of a fund's resources was to be returned to the university for the perpetuation and extension of its goals.* The accounts in this sub-series reveal the meticulous care taken by the treasurer to keep the records of the various investing funds distinct and well-ordered. Many of the funds represented are the same as those whose subscribers are recorded in the BENEFACTORS series.
  Real Estate includes the records of Yale's income producing land holdings, of the accounts of income derived from rent and land sales and of the expense of maintaining property. The sub-series begins with several folders containing Deeds and Other Records of Land Holdings. At first there are registers or inventories listing properties some of which include explanations of how Yale acquired particular tracts.